大家早上好，
good morning everyone
嗯，我想录制一个关于
um I want to record a quick tutorial on
如何在
how to actually improve faces
主要扩散中实际改善面部的快速教程，我不确定你是否
in staple diffusion I'm not sure if you
遇到了这个问题，你实际上
run into this issue where you actually
有一个稳定的扩散提示，或者
have like a stable diffusion prompt or
你正在尝试像模型一样运行 就像
you're trying to run like a model like a
劳拉一样，你正在创建
Laura and you're creating like a
一堆图像，其中一些
a bunch of image and some of them have
像扭曲的脸，你想
like a distorted face and you want to
修复它们，所以我将向你展示一个
fix them so I'm going to show you a
快速技巧让我们
quick trick let's bring a prompt here
从我运行的现有提示中获取提示 所以让我们
from an existing one I ran so let's
apply that gotta remove the model
在这里应用必须删除模型限制
restriction here
确保没有额外的网络
make sure there is no additional Network
加载一切都很好没有控制导航暗淡一切都
loaded all good no control navig dim all
很好所以只使用随机
good so just gonna go with the random
前面以便我们获得一些随机性
front so that we get some Randomness and
然后我们可以看到我们如何解决
then we can see how we can fix over
这些问题所以在这里我将
those issues so here I'm going to use
像我一直在研究的劳拉一样使用，
like a Laura I've been working on and
我注意到有时它会
I've noticed that sometimes it creates
在脸上造成一些问题，不是因为
um some issues with the face not because
模型不好，而是因为没有
the model is bad but because there is no
学习阶段的大小 这是
learned phase of the size that are part
渲染提示的一部分所以让我们渲染
of the render prompt so let's render
或让我们生成我应该说
or let's generate I should say
那些所以让我们做四个因为一个
those ones so let's do four because one
是不够的所以让
is not going to be enough so let's get
我们得到四个图像但是正如你在这里看到的
us four image but as you can see here we
那样我们已经可以看到
can already sort of see that the face is
在主题没有放大的特定较小版本中，脸部看起来不会很好，
not going to be looking good in that
particular smaller version where the
所以当你
subject is not zoomed in so when you
有一个距离很远的主题时，
have a subject that's kind of far away
脸部往往很糟糕，这就是
the face tends to be bad and that's
能够修复这些问题的好地方
where it's good to be able to sort of
有了这个技巧，我将向
fix those with the trick I'm going to
您展示，
show you
um
嗯，让我们继续为图像渲染那些，
so let's well let's keep rendering those
我们快完成了，然后
for image and we're almost done and then
我们将看看它们的
we're going to look at what they look
样子，所以如果我们看这个，是的，
like so if we look at this one yeah the
脸是 看起来有点奇怪 嘴唇
face is kind of looking weird there's
上方有一种奇怪的人工制品
sort of a weird artifact above the the
lips
同样这里的眼睛不好
same thing here the eyes are bad I face
it just generally bad this one's got bad
eyes and this one is sort of okay but I
guess we could probably improve it so
嗯，第一个，所以我们
let's work on uh the first one so we're
要选择第一个，然后
gonna go pick the first one and then
我们要把它发送给临时演员，所以我们
we're gonna send it to extras so we're
要把它发送给临时演员，我们
going to send that to extras and we're
要调整两个大小
gonna run a resize of two
，我喜欢运行 uh upscaler 叫
and I like to run the uh upscaler called
swinner
所以游泳 我猜是 swin IR 4X
so swim I guess swin IR 4X
没有 no face fix 没有类似的东西
and no no face fix no anything like that
we're just gonna run and double the
resolution of that
um
by running it through I guess the swin
IR upscaler
我们有一个
and there you go so now we have a
高档版本，但脸并没有
upscale version but the face is not
更好，对吧，我们仍然有坏
better right we still have like the bad
嘴，脸仍然看起来不太好，
mouth the face is still not looking good
所以你如何解决这个问题，现在你发送
so how do you fix that is now you send
这个升级版本，发送到油漆中，
this upscaled version to send to in the
paint
那将要做什么 它
what that's going to do and it's
实际上会带来呃实际的呃
actually going to bring uh the actual uh
图像但我也会在那里复制我的
image but I'm also going to copy my
原始提示
original prompt in there
所以我猜这里的技巧我想如果我把
so I guess the trick here I think if I
它从耳朵痛苦地发送到现在我有
send it to in pain from ear now I've got
错误的版本 图片，但如果
the wrong version of the picture but if
我返回提取图片并将该
I go back to extract and just send that
版本的图片发送
version of the picture
到
to
um in paint，
um in paint
那么现在我应该使用
so now I should have the higher
我的原始
resolution with my original
配置为提示和
configuration for the prompt and
所有内容提供更高分辨率，所以所有内容都应该在那里，
everything so everything should be there
所以我们现在想做什么 是遮住
so what we want to do now is mask the
脸，这样我们只画图的那
face such that we only in paint that
部分，所以我
portion of the diagram so I'm just going
要去选择那部分，我
to go and select that portion and I'm
要去这里，我会说
going to go here and I'm going to say
我只想画面具
that I only want to in paint mask the
蒙版部分，我想画什么是
Mask Part and I want to in paint what is
蒙版，所以蒙版模式不是付费面具，
mask so the mask mode isn't paid mask
然后我只想
and then the in paint area is I only
专注于画脸的这个区域
want to focus on in painting this area
，我想在
of the face and I want to give this in
画一个 512 x 512 的分辨率
painting a resolution of 512 by 512
大致正确，脸部有点方形，
roughly right the face is sort squarish
所以我们要走了，不要担心，
so we're gonna go and don't don't worry
如果那种显示它
if that kind of displays that it's going
会像那张照片的裁剪，它
to be like a crop of that picture it's
不会是因为我们' 如果我们只在
not going to be because we're doing only
蒙版区域内进行绘画，它
in painting within the masked area it's
只会以
just going to render that one part in
512 x 512 渲染该部分，并将
512 by 512 and it's going to replace the
用改进后的版本替换原始版本中的面部，
face in this original with the uh
所以让我们渲染它，
improved version so let's render it and
看看会发生什么让我们仔细
let's see what happens let's double
检查其他所有内容 75 是的，这是一个
check everything else 75 yeah that's a
很好的比例，我们只赢了一个所以让我们
good ratio we only won one so let's go
继续生成它，
ahead and generate it
你会马上看到
and you're going to see that right away
它开始看起来更像安娜的
it starts to look a lot more like Anna's
深帕尔马
deep parmes
，这就是你如何快速修复一张
and that is how you can quickly fix a
脸
face by in painting
使用你的原始模型只绘制面部的一部分，
just the portion of the face using your
在我的例子中它是劳拉，
original model in my case it was a Laura
它完全修复了
and it totally fixed the bad phase that
通过使用模型
was created by using what the model has
对模型本身的了解但通过将
learned about the model Itself by but by
其正确绘制成 512 x 512 而创建的不良阶段
properly painting it into a 512 by 512
分辨率 让我们快速写另一个，
resolution let's write another one
只是为了给你看 让我们再次选择
quickly just to show you let's pick the
第二个，它是一张相当小的脸
second one which was a fairly small face
我的意思是在整个图片中那是一张小脸
again I mean that's a small face in the
所以难怪它不是
whole picture so no wonder that it's not
那么好所以我们要发送
so great so we're I'm going to send it
我将再次生成它，
to extra again I'm going to generate so
这样我们就可以获得
that we get
实际的
the actual
um
高档版本，
upscale version
因为我们已经得到了我可以将它发送到
now that we've got that I can send it to
油漆中
in paint
，在这里
and here
我只是要确保是的，我们
I'm just going to make sure that yeah we
有种子减一 对于一个
have seed minus one for a seed that's
很好的种子，所以现在我们看到我们有像我
fine so now we see that we have like the
要走的脸一样，
face I'm gonna go and
只需选择那个区域，这样我们就可以
just select that area so that we just in
绘制那个部分，我仍然
paint that part and I still have that
选择了那个部分，所以让我们撤消这个让我们
part selected so let's undo this let's
撤消这个然后让我们
undo this and let's just select this one
在这里选择这一部分
part here
好吧现在生成
okay now generate
我我仍然有 512 哦不
I I still have like 512 oh no the
分辨率不是她实际上呃
resolution was not she was actually uh
更改为更高分辨率你知道
changed to a higher resolution you know
在这种情况下它并不重要
in this case it's not going to matter
它只是要去做一个更大的
it's just going to go and do a bigger
区域尽可能远 因为画布与
area as far as the canvas is concerned
图像的生成有关
for the for the generation of the image
并且它工作得很好你可以
and it worked quite well right you can
看到它实际上在为它
see that it's actually it actually did a
绘制正确的
pretty good job at in painting a proper
脸方面做得非常好我可以去改回
face into it I could go and change back
512 并重做 再次向您展示
to 512 and redo it again just to show
you that
512 x 512，我将开始
so 512 by 512 and I'm just gonna go and
生成，现在您将看到
generate and now you're gonna see that
它将更多地集中在
it's going to focus a lot more on just
那个部分，
that part
然后您就可以了，所以现在我们有了一个新的
and there you go so now we have a new in
画了脸，你可以生成
painted face and you can generate
多个版本这个版本是松弛的，
multiple versions this version was slaky
头部稍微向左转，
the head was slightly turned to the left
现在这个脸稍微多一点，
now this one is facing a little bit more
所以你可以做一堆渲染来获得
so you can do a bunch of renders to get
你想要的正确的脸，用于
the right face that you want for the in
绘画
painting
和 这就是你如何
and that's how you can quickly fix faces
在绘画中使用呃快速修复面部并使用
using uh in painting and using your
你想要使用的模型所以我希望
model that you want to use so I hope
这很有用它是一个快速教程
that was useful it's a quick tutorial
并且
and
喜欢
enjoy